

XRAVE110

CONTACTS



+48-577-082-718



xRave110@protonmail.com



portfolio-xrave110.vercel.app



A Jablonka, Poland

Technologies

C, Python

Solidity, Javascript

Toolsets/Frameworks

Pytest

Brownie, Web3, Git

Hardhat/Ethers, React

Truffle, OpenZeppelin

Other skills

Polish

DeFi

English, Ethereum, ISTQB

NFTs

Education

2012-2017

Cracov University of Technology Cracov

Electrical engineering with major in Electric Control Devices in full-time mode of study.

KAMIL **PALENIK**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer with 5 years experience in automotive industry. In 2019 I got interested in blockchain technology, especially in DeFi and I have been using DeFi protocols ever since. I was absolutely amazed how it works without any intermediares just maths and peers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dec 2019 - Now

Blockchain learning/development

Smart contracts development with brownie and unit/integration tests. One year course with Moralis Academy concerning smart contracts development, web3 interaction and web development. New projects development which consolidated skills and extended them to multiple frameworks and toolsets.

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022

Embedded System Software Integrator

Nexteer Automotive

Integration tests development. Components integration and configuration Autosar stack.

Nov 2019 - Mar 2022

Embedded System Software Engineer

Nexteer Automotive

Developing and testing software components using C, Python and Reactis/Matlab. Incorporating unit and integration testing for CAN messages.

Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

Embedded Software Engineer

VECTOR MICROSAR changes in basic software components (DEM, DCM). The same responsibilities as the previous role.

Oct 2017 - May 2019

Junior Embedded Software Engineer

Application component software development. Performing static and dynamic unit tests for components. Modeling software using SysML/UML.